You know, the one thing they don't want to talk about is the election.
They don't want to talk about it because they're guilty as hell.
They cheated like hell. They know it.
And you'll never find out all the ways.
But we don't need all the ways because, you know, it was, I think, 22,000 votes separated it.
And we have millions and millions of votes. It's a very sad thing.
So the most important part of what's coming up is to guard the vote.
And you should go into Detroit and you should go into Philadelphia
and you should go into some of these places, Atlanta,
and you should go into some of these places.
And we got to watch those votes when they come in,
when they're being, you know, shoved around in wheelbarrows
and dumped on the floor and everyone's saying, what's going on?
We're like a third world nation, a third world nation.
And we can't let it.
So this right here is just like a hat trick of racism.
OK, let me tell you why.
So firstly, when he's sitting here talking about the fact that
these are particular cities that need to be monitored,
he specifically says cities that we know to be very black cities.
OK, that is not by accident.
Nothing this man says is by accident.
Y'all know that he's reading something that somebody wrote that he's supposed to say on purpose.
Now, when he says, oh, these are places that are handling votes and ballots in a wheelbarrow.
And it's like a third world country.
Even just the use of the term third world country,
especially correlated to cities that we know have large black constituencies,
is, again, not by accident and racist.
It's racist because when he uses the term third world country,
what he's talking about is a country that he feels is not developed at the level of civility,
of resources, of elevation as America.
And we all know that the actual third world countries are recovering economies
that have been depleted, OK, that have been disrupted and disturbed by colonizers like America.
Last but not least, what he's talking about is voter intimidation.
Now, he may frame it as, oh, you all need to go watch the polls, but that's not what's happening here.
He's talking about voter intimidation.
And we've seen voter intimidation as recent as the midterm elections.
But a more profound example is during the 50s, the 40s, the 30s, the 60s,
during the time when black people were fighting for the right to vote as citizens of this country.
And they would show up in Klan outfits.
They would show up with weapons.
They would show up and physically assault black people who were trying to exercise their right to vote.
And they had black people staying home because they were like,
it ain't even worth getting a black eye over this.
That's where we're going.
When they say make America great again, that's what they're talking about.
They want to go back to an America where you can stop black people from voting with physical, actual violence.
Right now, they're just doing it with, you know, gerrymandering and laws.
Nah, they want to beat that ass away from the polls.
Because they don't want you to be represented in the polls.
A vote is like proof of life.
And black people voting is like saying that we actually exist.
And they're like, nah, not in this country.
And so whatever illusions you have about this person actually caring about black people,
please, please do not lie to yourself.
Know who the devil is when they show you who they are.
I'm not going to lie to you.
And I'm not going to lie to you because they're like I don't know who to say that.
I don't know.
No.